Why?
Why the hell did your
heart stop beating, Dad?
I don't believe my
father is actually dead.
I think he'll be okay if
I can get his stand back.
I can help you.
I can explain these new abilities.
What you have is called a stand power.
I need to see her.
I've got questions, Jolene Cujo.
I see.
So, Ermes has a stand too.
And about the discs.
I know it sounds crazy, but
I'm telling you the truth.
When Ermes put the memory disc back into
McQueen, he suddenly came back to life.
It's like he regenerated.
If we can somehow retrieve
those discs, Jolene,
then I have complete faith
your father will surely...
So tell me, what'd you do with
the discs that were in that man?
I'm keeping them safe with me.
They're both right here.
If Ermes were to take them into her cell,
the guards would definitely
find them during the body check.
I won't be giving the
stand disc back to him,
but I'll return the disc with his
memories after some time passes.
McQueen's memory disk.
On this CD, there are memories that can
give me some idea of who's behind Palesnake.
And maybe, even memories about
the disks from my old man.
It's coming!
Hurry up!
Help me with the door!
Who's minding my business doing my job?
All I did was touch the tire!
Why is this happening?
Just hurry!
Get your ass in here!
We gotta close the door!
Get up and help me out!
It's so happy!
Give us your all!
You're almost there!
Keep pulling!
What's wrong with you?
Pull harder or we're
both gonna die in here!
Bro, those ain't my arms.
What the hell? I know.
The one who wasn't pulling
hard enough was me.
Get out of here before it's too late!
No!
Now, what's the truth?
Don't cry to it that's
Radio of the needle and
get raised and move It's
all been around We won't
touch it Okay?
All right!
My little survival day!
Get away from No water I!
don't wanna fade Let's start! Go!
1, 2, 3 Can we find a way?
Break out!
We're coming out!
don't stop beating, don't
stop beating, I'm mad!
who were working on the farm
suddenly disappeared without a trace.
Are you serious?
Oh wow, that is absolutely awful.
It's unthinkable that these two
inmates were able to escape.
Could they have fallen into a marshland
and drowned or been bitten by a snake?
Regardless, we have to do everything
we can to find those two right now.
Why aren't you considering
the possibility that
an alligator could have
had them for breakfast?
Might have been a female one.
Hold it, which one of
you said that nonsense?
No way, I did do such thing.
My diet is criminal-free, thank you!
Hmm.
Well, on to business.
We're putting together a
search party and I'll be
needing a slight few of
you ladies to do the deed.
You will not receive compensation, nor will
any time be docked from your sentences.
I'm merely requesting you help us
out of the kindness of your heart.
Any volunteers?
What are you doing, Jolene?
You literally just got out of solitary.
Why are you trying to tire
yourself out even more?
Maybe because you're
not going to be there.
What?
Now, let's see.
Five of you should do.
Guard, I'll leave the precautions to you.
In order to prevent any attempts at
escaping, we've got these nifty bracelets.
All inmates going to
the farm must wear them.
We call them like a virgins, but
they're also known as invisible bars.
I'm only going to say this once.
If you hit these with any type of force,
try taking them off or even destroy them.
They will explode immediately.
Also, I have the base unit on my wrist.
If you go any more than 50
meters away, they'll detonate.
Let me tell you,
it's going to be really hard to wipe
your ass if you don't have a wrist.
All right, you five, show me some hustle!
Fifty meters, huh?
Do we have to run to keep up with you?
Wait just a second! Hey!
Okay, from here we'll split up
and search in every direction.
That grassy thicket you
see over there is a marsh,
and it's chock-full of alligators,
so watch where you're trekking!
Safe to say it's not in here.
Why'd you volunteer for
this scavenger hunt, Jolene?
Though I am glad you decided to come
along I've got a few questions for you.
And I'd like some answers about
this whole disc situation and more.
Importantly this pale snake guy I've
heard so much about before that answer.
This did you see what was on that disc
the one from the inmate named McQueen?
Huh yeah I gave it a look over but
messing with that thing made me feel.
Horrible whenever I touched it this
awful smell assaulted my senses so you.
Didn't notice it then huh if you take
a closer look at the footage that was.
Recorded you'll see there's a clue that
could reveal Palesnake's intentions.
McCree my child this disc is perfect for
you it'll suit you well it shall be yours.
Please now, take this
Stand ability and prosper.
He's got more of these stockpiled
in the farm tractor's tire?
There had to be at least two dozen
more discs hidden away in there.
Understand what he's trying to do now?
He's probably been robbing Stand users,
taking their memories and abilities
for his personal collection.
With the amount of discs
that he's gathered together,
he'd need to make sure other inmates
and guards couldn't discover them?
hence the secluded hiding spot.
No one would ever check a tire.
My dad's might be there too.
The discs with Star
Platinum and his memories
have got to be hidden away with the rest.
Huh? Your dad?
So the whole reason you're doing
this is to find your dad's?
Anyway.
Sorry, but that's about all I
know regarding this situation.
I'm gonna go look for that tractor
We're looking for a tractor, huh?
Seeing as we're on a farm, there
are probably gonna be a lot of them.
That storehouse Hmm.
Hey!
You two ladies sure look like you're
having a grand old time over here.
What do you think you're
out here for, a picnic?
Cut the chitchat and get to search it.
Actually, we were just about to
check that building over there.
If you'll excuse me.
You're the one who made us
chase you like dogs earlier.
I'd say it's you who's having fun.
Hold it! You there!
Did you say something just now?
Nah, not particularly.
I was only given my
solemn vow to run around
this farm and search
like a good little dog.
Ah, she rubs me the wrong way. Huh?
Looks like an alligator's.
I told you, hold it right there!
Who do you think you
are looking down on me?
I'm the one in charge here!
Pass!
That was a complete accident, you know.
It was a coincidence that my baton was
swinging at the same spot as your wrist.
Why is it making this sound?
This doesn't mean what I
think it does, does it?
I didn't actually hit
that thing, you know.
You saw what happened, it was an accident.
Blame yourself.
Hey, this thing ain't gonna
go on for real, is it?
Haha, real funny.
Now just make it stop, please.
Hey, hey now, don't go
waving that thing over here.
If it were to explode near me, well,
that'd be bad news for everyone.
Wait a second, I'm sorry for what I said.
Really, I mean it.
Hey, be careful, Missy.
Get any closer to me and
we're gonna have a problem.
I'm begging you!
Just make this damn noise go
away before my wrist goes slow!
Hell yeah!
That ought to cheat you!
You're falling right on
top of some alligator shit!
Stopped beeping.
Oh dear, stop panicking, Hermes.
That fall could have been real bad.
Don't you see that beeping
was just there to warn you?
You weren't in any
danger, right, Mr. Guard?
Piece of shit, Guard.
What the hell's with that guy?
So that stand was yours, huh?
What the heck?
Why'd we even look here?
There's only a tractor and
bags of flour everywhere.
There's no point in even checking inside.
If they could be found here,
they wouldn't have needed a stupid
search party in the first place.
What?
Are you serious right now?
Look, that's gotta be it, Jolene.
I think you're right.
It's the same shape as the tractor
we saw from the discs recording.
Same number, too.
Yeah, it's got the same vehicle number.
Four, just like the disc.
They should be in that tire.
If we can remove it, we'll
find the discs inside.
Listen carefully!
We will now be moving our
search to the marshland!
It's possible that our
two missing convicts
were attacked by gators
or drowned in the water.
Now get swimming!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who exactly do you think
is getting in that water?
Because it ain't gonna be me.
Let's go!
He can ride that on land and water?
You've got to be kidding me.
If we step foot in that marsh,
we're just asking for diseases.
This is so annoying.
Let's take it off.
Now's our chance to remove that tire.
Hey, Jolene, you feel that?
Something real strange is going on here.
I mean, this is definitely bizarre. Yeah,
if we don't remove the tire right now,
the guard will keep moving
farther away from us.
That's not what I'm saying.
Don't you remember what the
chief said when we started?
he mentioned five people, right?
Before we left, he definitely
said five of you should be fine.
But now there are six of us.
Hey, Jolene, what the hell
do you think is going on?
If you include the two of us...
There are six of us here!
I'm pretty sure when we took off
earlier, there were only five.
But I never took a good look
at the other girls' faces.
Jolene, do you see the same thing?
I can't say for sure.
I was so focused on running.
Although, everyone is wearing a handcuff.
This is weird.
Were there always six of us here?
I mean, from the beginning?
Yo, what'd you just say?
So you noticed it too, huh?
You're thinking that when
we all first started,
there were only five of us, aren't you?
Do you have any idea when and who came in?
Not really, and I might just be mistaken.
Besides, it doesn't really
matter how many there are.
I can vouch for her.
She was with me from the beginning.
I remember her.
Her name is Atro.
I always see her getting bullied.
You volunteered for this search
because your bullies didn't come along.
That right?
Sorry, but I have no
idea who you are. Hey!
Wait, hold on!
What's happening?
I didn't do anything!
Why is my handcuff beeping?
Mine is, too!
Yeah, same here!
Hey, what the hell?
Now everyone's cuff is beeping!
The motorbike went more
than 50 meters away!
But how?
It shouldn't be that far.
The guard isn't there anymore.
Where did he go?
The motorbike is covered in blood.
Why, though?
I think I know why all
the cuffs keep beeping.
It's gotta be because the
guard's body is moving
farther and farther
away from where we are.
Could he have fallen into the
water and is being washed away?
Just find that stupid prick.
Wherever he is, he's
more than 50 meters away.
The pain's good!
Hey, you guys!
This is bad!
Mine is getting really fast!
There's no way!
She's dead.
Could it be the additional
person decided to attack?
Is it because we got too close to those
discs hidden away in the storehouse?
Look 50 meters in the opposite
direction from the girl that blew up.
He's over there!
Let's get to the guard, hurry!
If we're close to him, this beeping
will stop and we won't explode too!
Hey, watch your back, Jolene.
No doubt the enemy has got to be one of
those three girls and an enraged psychopath.
Personally, I already know
who I'm suspicious of.
I bet it's that chick with the undercut.
I mean, the girl who blew up did
say she didn't know who she was.
It's gotta be her, I'm telling you!
She used her stand to take out the guard!
And before she kills us,
we gotta get the bitch!
Hold on a second, Hermes.
Let's say our culprit
is who you think it is.
If that were the case,
doesn't that mean she would
have been guarding the
discs in that storehouse
since before we showed up?
Yeah, I guess that's just about right.
But that's impossible.
She's still a prisoner.
And there's no way a prisoner
can guard something 24-7.
Joanne, stand back!
Something is in there!
What?
Where?
Stay the hell away from the water!
There's something in this bucket!
Hermes, hey, did you
really see something? No.
I guess it was nothing.
But still, I won't be going
in this marsh ever again.
Stay close, Jolene.
The last thing we need is to
get separated from each other.
Especially since we have
no idea who the enemy is.
You're right.
And we've still got these
troublesome handcuffs to deal with.
In order to take the
discs from the storehouse,
we have to make sure we
stay within 50 meters of
the guard's body and the
three other prisoners.
Hermes!
What the shit was in that bucket?
It grabbed my face out of nowhere!
What is that thing?
Some kind of demented flea?
It split in two!
No, now there's four of them!
What are they?
It was stupid to think that there
wasn't anything in the bucket.
If i'd taken a second
to look more carefully,
i'd have seen that there were
countless little bastards?
It's swimming in the water!
Back!
Hermes, you're...
Jolene, stay away!
This water is a death trap and it's
getting deadlier by the second!
I don't know how, but the
stand multiplies in the water!
Get out of here!
You can't catch up!
This is all part of the stand's plan!
Stone Ocean!
Don't worry, I'll save you!
Jolene, she's walking on woven threads?
But if you're using that much thread,
doesn't that mean you're losing body mass?
every time you take a step over here?
Jolene, just get out of the water!
Save yourself, I can take care of this!
Ah, Ura!
Impossible!
Yes, that's right.
It definitely feels impossible.
Good freaking grief.
If I hadn't taken out all of that thread
from my body, I'd be dead right now.
This thing's power.
Her guts are completely hollow.
Oh, she let that thing hit her
so she could grab it's hand!
Jolene, we have to hurry
and get out of the water!
Don't stand up just yet, Hermes!
That parasitic fuck is really just a
bunch of tiny stands clustered together!
They were hiding in the
water of the bucket I kicked.
Then when I turned around,
they dragged me in!
I understand that.
That's why I'm asking you not to stand up.
You gotta grab onto it under the water!
The thread that I'm releasing!
It's quick!
Powerful too, but the speed's crazy!
What the hell is that thing?
As the stand moves farther away from its
user, it should become weaker and slower!
Son of a...
Calm down, Jolene.
I gave our pursuer here a stigma.
I managed to slap one on it
when I was caught in its arms.
This is what my stand can do.
I'll rip it off now!
Get back!
Away from the water!
It's not coming onto land.
As I thought, it can only attack when
its prey is in the water with it.
Please respond!
This is prisoner number FE-32125!
It's an emergency!
The guard got into an accident!
Somebody please just hurry up and help us!
What the hell is going
on with the two of you?
It almost looked as though you were
running on top of the water earlier.
Stop right there!
Unless you want to die, move!
All three of you, get away from the water!
Don't go trying to do anything funny.
The enemy here is one of you!
If we want to grab the
discs in the storehouse,
first we have to take
care of the stand user.
Although you think I cope
My head is filled with hope
Of some place other than here
Although you think I smile
Inside and all the while
I'm wondering About my destiny
I'm thinking
about Out all the
things I'd like
to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming for me.
From today
Thank you.